<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. -->
    <string name="app_name">Oviedo Tour Guide</string>

    <!-- Title for the description of the image. -->
    <string name="locationImage">Location Image</string>

    <!-- Categories (tabs). -->
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>
    <string name="category_history">History</string>
    <string name="category_museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>

    <!-- Details of each location -->

    <!-- Santa María del Naranco -->
    <string name="santamaria_title">Santa María del Naranco</string>
    <string name="santamaria_info">The Palace of Ramiro I on Mount Naranco is a unique building without a clear–cut purpose (palace, church, royal pavilion, royal hall, etc.). The building has a rectangular ground plan and is divided into two floors connected by an external stairway. The lower floor, or crypt, is completely sealed, while the upper floor is open.\n\nThe building, painstakingly executed in masonry, is raised on a stone base affording it a vertical sense that is reinforced by the fluted buttresses that reach the roof.\n\nThe lower floor, or crypt, is similar to that of Santa Leocadia in the Holy Chamber. It is accessed from the outside and is fully reinforced with transversal ribs.\n\nThe upper floor is accessed via the external stairway. This is a single room with balconies on both sides and mullioned windows that simulate another floor on one side.\n\nThe balconies are divided into three arches that rest on columns with carved shafts and Corinthian capitals. Outside, fluted pilasters with crosses drape down alongside the windows, ending in medallions with animal and human figuration.\n\nThe inside, which is fully vaulted, is traversed by transversal ribs that repeat the exterior decoration of decorated pilasters ending in medallions.</string>
    <string name="santamaria_timetable">Winter (01/10 to 31/03)\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:30pm\nMonday and Sunday: 10:00am–12:30pm\n\nSummer (01/04 to 30/09):\nTuesday to Saturday: 9:30am–1:00pm and 3:30pm–7:00pm\nMonday and Sunday: 9:30am–1:00pm</string>

    <!-- Cathedral of San Salvador -->
    <string name="catedralsansalvador_title">Cathedral of San Salvador</string>
    <string name="catedralsansalvador_info">Oviedo Cathedral has its origins in the basilica built by King Alfonso II The Chaste (791–842) dedicated to San Salvador (the Holy Saviour). It was built on the ruins of an earlier church ordered built by his father, Fruela I, in 765 and destroyed thirty years later by the Moors. This king also had the Church of Santa María and the royal palace built to the north and south, respectively, of the original basilica of San Salvador.\n\nConstruction of the Gothic cathedral began in the 14th century, demolishing the previous Romanesque and Pre–Romanesque basilica. Building work received a definitive impetus during the Bishopric of Gutierre de Toledo (1377–1389). The construction was completed in the mid–16th century, with the crowning of the tower in a late Gothic style. That is to say, the building of the cathedral lasted nearly three centuries. And it was still necessary to work for another hundred years to build the chapels and tombs that can be seen today adjoining the aisles. Therefore, the construction of the present cathedral took about four hundred years, with particular intensity during the 15th century, a period during which the predominant style was that known as ornate or Flamboyant Gothic, a style within which this cathedral may be included.\n\nThe building is divided into three naves, the larger central nave and the side naves with chapels between the buttresses, preceded by a portico. The outstanding transept brings a Latin cross layout to the ground plan, topped by a polygonal apse containing the ambulatory. The verticality of the walls, achieved via pointed arches separating the naves, a blind triforium and a clerestory with decorative windows. The entire cathedral (naves and chapels) is covered with groin vaulting, outstanding among which is the octagonal vaulting of the central nave.</string>
    <string name="catedralsansalvador_timetable">November to February\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:00pm and 4:00pm–6:00pm\n\nMarch, April, May and October\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:00pm and 4:00pm–7:00pm\n\nJune\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:00pm and 4:00pm–8:00pm\n\nJuly and August\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–8:00pm\n\nSeptember\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–7:00pm and from 14th to 21st, 10:00am–5:00pm</string>

    <!-- San Pelayo Monastery -->
    <string name="monasteriosanpelayo_title">San Pelayo Monastery</string>
    <string name="monasteriosanpelayo_info">The Benedictine Monastery of San Pelayo was founded in the Middle Ages dedicated to St John the Baptist. However, with the transfer of the remains of St Pelagius to Oviedo to be deposited in this convent, it changed its name to the Monastery of San Pelayo.\n\nIt is a cloistered convent that forms part of the history of Asturias, as it has managed to amass an outstanding collection of documents during its thousand years of existence and currently serves as the Provincial Historical Archives. The nuns who occupy it have traditionally been known as \"las Pelayas\".\n\nIn its splendid archives can found collections from the monasteries of San Bartolomé de Nava, Santa María de Villamayor, San Vicente and Santa María de la Vega, alongside many objects and relics that have come to form part of the convent.\n\nThe church was built between 1592 and 1600. It has a simple ground plan, a single nave without any chapels. The simple façade, between side walls and above an elongated staircase, is built with perfectly hewn ashlar. It consists of three doorways with mouldings, the central one being higher. Above this, there is a large niche with the stone figure of St Pelagius and a glass rose window. The interior is majestic, thanks to the choir stalls which came from the old Convent of San Vicente. Carved in wood in the late 16th century, they are simply made in the Mannerist style. They comprise thirty–six seats of honour with an extensive iconographic repertoire on the backs, where kings and emperors are portrayed.\n\nThe ornate façade of the vicarage was designed in 1703, based on the design of Baroque palaces. The ground floor has three large arches between free–standing Tuscan columns that support the balconies on the first floor, which are decorated with lugged architraves between Ionic columns. The second floor bears the coats of arms of the Benedictine Order, below the royal coat of arms, which is situated between two Corinthian columns on a prominent attic below the curved pediment.\n\nThe cloister has three levels that make it a solid construction with a certain monumental air. Like the church, the cloister is supported by pillars and Tuscan columns.\n\nIn the 17th century, the old bell tower was replaced by a new tower topped with a Gothic tracery spire, reproducing at a smaller scale the verticality of the cathedral tower.</string>
    <string name="monasteriosanpelayo_timetable">Sundays and holidays\nLauds 08: 30\nEucharist 11: 00\nVespers 19: 00\n\nWorking days\nLauds 08: 30\nVespers and Eucharist 19:00\n\nSaturdays and Vespers of holidays\nLauds and Eucharist 08: 00\nVespers 7:00 p.m.</string>

    <!-- Holy Chamber -->
    <string name="camarasanta_title">Holy Chamber</string>
    <string name="camarasanta_info">Commissioned by Alfonso II the Chaste, the Holy Chamber is the place that safeguards Asturias\' most valuable treasures: the Cross of the Angels, symbol of the city of Oviedo, and the Victory Cross, a symbol of Asturias emblazoned on the flag. What is believed to be the Holy Shroud of Christ is also safeguarded here.\n\nThe Holy Chamber is rectangular and has two floors; the lower one, called the Chapel or Crypt of Santa Leocadia, is covered with a barrel vault supported on plinths with coarse lunettes, while the upper floor, the Chapel of San Miguel, is divided into three sections, retaining the original apse, while the rest dates from the second half of the 12th century. It is covered with a barrel vault reinforced with three transversal ribs supported on six limestone columns, to which pairs of statues of the twelve Apostles areaffixed.\n\nAlso embedded in the wall inside above the entrance door are three heads carved in stone, corresponding to a Crucifixion which originally also held painted bodies. Today, the painted part has totally disappeared.</string>
    <string name="camarasanta_timetable">November to February\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:00pm and 4:00pm–6:00pm.\n\nMarch, April, May and October\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:00pm and 4:00pm–7:00pm.\n\nJune\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–2:00pm and 4:00pm–8:00pm.\n\nJuly and August\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–8:00pm.\n\nSeptember\nMonday to Saturday: 10:00am–7:00pm and from 14th to 21st, 10:00am–5:00pm.\n\nIt will remain closed to visitors on Sundays and Holy Days of Obligation, and on Saturdays from 6 pm.\n\nWhenever liturgical celebrations are being held, there are only \"partial\" visits (Holy Chamber, Museum and Cloister)</string>

    <!-- Old Town -->
    <string name="cascohistorico_title">Old Town</string>
    <string name="cascohistorico_info">The historic center of Oviedo responds to Oviedo round, the medieval city that was inside the wall of which remains are still preserved in the streets Paraíso and Jovellanos and in the Plaza de Riego. It is located in the center of the city and presided over by the most important architectural, cultural and historical building: the Cathedral.\n\nThe set consists of three axes: the first dominate the Cathedral, the Plaza de la Constitución, where the Town Hall is located, or the Plaza de Riego, with its respective buildings. The second axis is marked by the Plaza del Paraguas, Calle Santa Ana or Calle Mon, heart of the city\'s nightlife, with numerous bars and pubs. Finally, the third axis consists of the Corrada del Obispo or Calle San Vicente, where the so–called Monastery of San Pelayo is located, occupied by cloistered nuns affectionately nicknamed 'the Pelayas'.\n\nAll this makes up the old town, within which you can perform a variety of cultural activities, visiting the Cathedral, the Museum of Fine Arts, the Archaeological Museum, or playful, enjoying the wide variety of bars, pubs and nightclubs.</string>
    <string name="cascohistorico_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Historical building of the old University of Oviedo -->
    <string name="universidadoviedo_title">Historical building of the old University of Oviedo</string>
    <string name="universidadoviedo_info">Located in the historic center of the city, on San Francisco Street, it is the first construction of the University of Oviedo. The building remained a teaching space until the 1980s and now houses some of the central services of the university such as the Rector\'s Office or the General Secretariat. It was inaugurated on September 21, 1608 and initially hosted the studies of Arts, Canons, Laws and Theology, although in 1618 the studies were expanded.\n\nDue to the October Revolution of 1934 and the Civil War, all the funds of the library were lost, which was completely destroyed, and the rest of the building suffered great damages. In the middle of the 20th century, reconstruction proceeded according to the original style and new buildings and campuses were created to move the different studios.</string>
    <string name="universidadoviedo_timetable">Summer schedule\nFROM 01/07 TO 31/08\nMonday 08:00 – 20:00\nTuesday 08:00 – 20:15\nWednesday 08:00 – 20:00\nThursday 08:00 – 20:00\nFriday 08:00 – 20:00\nSaturday Closed\nSunday closed\n\nWinter time\nFROM 01/09 TO 06/30\nMonday 08:00 – 20:00\nTuesday 08:00 – 20:15\nWednesday 08:00 – 20:00\nThursday 08:00 – 20:00\nFriday 08:00 – 20:00\nSaturday 09:00 – 14:00\nSunday closed</string>

    <!-- Basilica of San Juan El Real -->
    <string name="basilicasanjuan_title">Basilica of San Juan El Real</string>
    <string name="basilicasanjuan_info">It is a Catholic temple that is located in Melquiades Cabal Street, right in the center of Oviedo. Of predominantly neo-Romanesque style, it was built in 1912 to replace the Romanesque church that collapsed in 1882.\n\nWhat stands out about this temple is its magnitude, because it has a considerable size for the space in which it is located. For this reason it receives the nickname of \'Cathedral of the Ensanche\'. Once inside, it is worth observing its imposing stained glass windows of Gothic inspiration.\n\nFrom its origin it is a parish church, but also with the title of minor basilica by decree of the Holy See since September 24, 2014.\n\nAs a curiosity, it is worth mentioning that in this church in 1923 the celebration of the marriage between Francisco Franco and Carmen Polo took place, which was of Oviedo origin. Likewise, her daughter Carmen Franco was baptized in this same church.</string>
    <string name="basilicasanjuan_timetable"></string>

    <!-- San Julian de los Prados -->
    <string name="sanjuliandelosprados_title">San Julian de los Prados</string>
    <string name="sanjuliandelosprados_info">This Oviedo church is the oldest and largest pre-Romanesque work in all of Spain, and has been declared an Artistic Heritage and World Heritage Site. Although the exact date of its construction is not known, it was ordered by King Alfonso II el Casto, around the 9th century.\n\nThe temple presents the characteristics of the pre-Romanesque style, such as the semicircular arches or the basilica. Also, they emphasize the paintings that decorate the walls of the church and of which still a significant part is conserved. It produces a great impact to penetrate in its interior, not only due to the paintings, but also to the sensation of amplitude that provides the width of the central ship, as well as the luminosity that the windows offer.</string>
    <string name="sanjuliandelosprados_timetable">Hours from July to September\nFROM 01/07 TO 30/09\nMonday 10:00 – 13:00\nTuesday 09:30 – 13:00, 16:00 – 18:00\nWednesday 09:30 – 13:00, 16:00 – 18:00\nThursday 09:30 – 13:00, 16:00 – 18:00\nFriday 09:30 – 13:00, 16:00 – 18:00\nSaturday 09:30 – 12:30, 16:00 – 18:00\nSunday closed\nClosed: Sunday, holidays and 1 and 6 of January, 2 of May, 8 and 25 of December.\n\nSchedule from October to April\nFROM 01/10 TO 04/30\nMonday 10:00 – 12:00\nTuesday 10:00 – 12:00\nWednesday 10:00 – 12:00\nThursday 10:00 – 12:00\nFriday 10:00 – 12:00\nSaturday 10:00 – 12:00\nSunday closed\nClosed: Sunday, holidays and 1 and 6 of January, 2 of May, 8 and 25 of December.\n\nSchedule for May and June\nFROM 01/05 TO 06/30\nMonday 10:00 – 12:30\nTuesday 10:00 – 12:30, 16:00 – 18:00\nWednesday 10:00 – 12:30, 16:00 – 18:00\nThursday 10:00 – 12:30, 16:00 – 18:00\nFriday 10:00 – 12:30, 16:00 – 18:00\nSaturday 10:00 – 12:30, 16:00 – 18:00\nSunday closed\nClosed: Sunday, holidays and 1 and 6 of January, 2 of May, 8 and 25 of December.</string>

    <!-- Campoamor Theater -->
    <string name="teatrocampoamor_title">Campoamor Theater</string>
    <string name="teatrocampoamor_info">Known worldwide for hosting the Princess of Asturias Awards, the Campoamor Theater is the most outstanding cultural center in Oviedo. Its construction took place between 1883 and 1890, although it was not inaugurated until 1892 and since then, hosts a large number of shows including opera, theater, dance, zarzuela and various concerts.\n\nIt owes its name to the Asturian poet Ramón de Campoamor, proposed by the then councilor of the city Leopoldo Alas \"Clarín\". It is the Opera Theater of Oviedo and has annual seasons of Opera and Zarzuela, being the only Spanish theater that offers a lyrical season throughout the year.\n\nIn addition to the Princess Awards, there are also the Campoamor Theater Lyric Awards and the Teatulias del Campoamor, to which writers such as Almudena Grandes or Ray Loriga come. You can check its programming on the official page.</string>
    <string name="teatrocampoamor_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Las Caldas Baths -->
    <string name="balneariocaldas_title">Las Caldas Baths</string>
    <string name="balneariocaldas_info">Located in the town of Las Caldas in the parish of Priorio, within the municipality of Oviedo. It is a complex that opened its doors for the first time in 1776. In 2003 it closed its doors for the first time to undergo a profound renovation after which it has become a center of reference in the thermal tourism of northern Spain.\n\nThe spa was built in Las Caldas taking advantage of thermal waters rich in carbonates and trace elements with a temperature of 40ºC. During the first half of the 19th century it enjoyed great popularity and became one of the main healing centers for northern Spain, especially for joint or bone pain, such as rheumatism.\n\nTourists and neighbors usually attend this center, because it is worth moving to this town of Oviedo to enjoy a pleasant stay in this spa and benefit from its thermal waters.</string>
    <string name="balneariocaldas_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Museum of Fine Arts of Asturia -->
    <string name="museobellasartes_title">Museum of Fine Arts of Asturia</string>
    <string name="museobellasartes_info">An apostolate by El Greco, the portrait that Goya made to Jovellanos on the beach of San Lorenzo or the light of Sorolla on the Valencian beaches. The Museum of Fine Arts of Asturias preserves one of the best national collections of art, with 15,000 pieces from the 14th to the 21st centuries.\n\nLocated in the heart of the old town, strolling through this museum is to visit, also, the Velarde Palace, the House of Oviedo-Portal or the recent expansion designed by Pachi Mangado, with views of the Cathedral Square.\n\nThe Fine Arts collection alternates the great names of Spanish painting, sculpture, applied and industrial arts with a careful selection of Asturian masters, such as Darío de Regoyos, Evaristo Arce, Nicanor Piñole, Aurelio Suárez, Orlando Pelayo and Luis Fernández.</string>
    <string name="museobellasartes_timetable">Summer time (July and August)\nFROM 01/07 TO 31/08\nClosed Monday\nTuesday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:00 – 20:00\nWednesday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:00 – 20:00\nThursday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:00 – 20:00\nFriday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:00 – 20:00\nSaturday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:00 – 20:00\nSunday 10:30 – 2:30\nHolidays from 11:30 a.m. to 2:30 p.m.\n\nWinter time\nFROM 01/09 TO 06/30\nClosed Monday\nTuesday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:30 – 20:30\nWednesday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:30 – 20:30\nThursday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:30 – 20:30\nFriday 10:30 – 14:00, 16:30 – 20:30\nSaturday 11:30 – 14:00, 17:00 – 20:00\nSunday 11:30 – 2:30\nHolidays from 11:30 a.m. to 2:30 p.m.</string>

    <!-- Archaeological Museum of Asturias -->
    <string name="museoarqueologico_title">Archaeological Museum of Asturias</string>
    <string name="museoarqueologico_info">Only for its location, the old cloister of the convent of San Vicente, the Archaeological Museum of Asturias, declared a National Monument in 1934, is one of the important visits in the city.\n\nIt opened its doors in 1952, however, due to the state of the building, in 1998 the procedures for its restoration began. The works began in 2004 but had to be modified by the surprising discovery of a bastion of the old wall of Oviedo of the 8th century. Since its discovery, the remains of the wall are one of its archaeological gems.\n\nIt has a permanent exhibition designed for all types of public distributed over three floors. Its purpose is to make an interactive tour through the history of the Asturian territory divided into five thematic areas, from Prehistory to the Late Middle Ages. One of its main attractions is the world of the Neanderthals, which highlights a hyperrealist reproduction of a Neanderthal woman. In addition to this exhibition, it has another temporary, a library and a space for teaching workshops.\n\nThe institution of the museum is responsible for conserving the archaeological legacy of Asturias through the functions of conservation and dissemination of heritage, such as the Asturian pre-Romanesque group or the Palaeolithic rock art.</string>
    <string name="museoarqueologico_timetable">Closed Monday\nTuesday closed\nWednesday 09:30 – 20:00\nThursday 09:30 – 20:00\nFriday 09:30 – 20:00\nSaturday 09:30 – 14:00, 17:00 – 20:00\nSunday 09:30 – 15:00\nHolidays from 09:30 to 15:00</string>
    
    <!-- Reception and Interpretation Center of Asturian Pre-Romanesque -->
    <string name="centroprerromanico_title">Reception and Interpretation Center of Asturian Pre-Romanesque</string>
    <string name="centroprerromanico_info">This center located on Mount Naranco collects the necessary information on the pre-Romanesque in Asturias. Just a few meters from the churches Santa María del Naranco and San Miguel de Lillo, both belonging to this style, allows the visitor to make a tour of the different stages of this style linked to the own political evolution of the Kingdom of Asturias, among the VIII and X centuries, with the help of maps, photographs and plans.\n\nThanks to its location, visitors can enjoy a pleasant panoramic view of Oviedo, since this center is located on the side of one of the mountains that surrounds the city. You can also choose to do some of the hiking trails that run through the vicinity of the museum.</string>
    <string name="centroprerromanico_timetable">Summer schedule\nFROM 01/07 TO 31/08\nClosed now\nMonday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nTuesday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nWednesday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nThursday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nFriday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nSaturday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nSunday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 19:30\nHolidays from 10:00 to 14:00 and from 15:30 to 18:30\n\nSchedule from October to December\nFROM 01/10 TO 12/31\nClosed Monday\nTuesday closed\nWednesday 10:00 – 13:30, 15:30 – 18:00\nThursday 10:00 – 13:30, 15:30 – 18:00\nFriday 10:00 – 13:30, 15:30 – 18:00\nSaturday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 18:30\nSunday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:00 – 18:30\nHolidays from 10:00 to 14:00 and from 15:30 to 18:30 h. January closed\n\nSchedule from February to June\nFROM 01/02 TO 06/30\nClosed Monday\nTuesday closed\nWednesday 10:00 – 13:30, 15:30 – 18:00\nThursday 10:00 – 13:30, 15:30 – 18:00\nFriday 10:00 – 13:30, 15:30 – 18:00\nSaturday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 18:30\nSunday 10:00 – 14:00, 15:30 – 18:30\nHolidays from 10:00 to 14:00 and from 15:30 to 18:30 h. January closed</string>

    <!-- Winter Park -->
    <string name="parqueinvierno_title">Winter Park</string>
    <string name="parqueinvierno_info">This park is one of the largest green areas of Oviedo and is located south of the city. It has about 1,000 square meters and from it you can enjoy the views of the Sierra del Aramo.\n\nIn its interior there are also other municipal facilities such as the Palace of Children or the open pools of San Lazaro, as well as a labyrinth formed by 650 laurels, a skating track and a typical Asturian quintana, formed by a large house and a hórreo.\n\nThis is, therefore, a park that you can go for a walk or to sit admiring its views, but also offers various activities to develop. In addition, this green area links directly with the Fuso de la Reina pedestrian path, which is an important spot for hiking enthusiasts.</string>
    <string name="parqueinvierno_timetable"></string>
    
    <!-- Green Route -->
    <string name="sendaverde_title">Green Route</string>
    <string name="sendaverde_info">Also known as Fuso de la Reina because it ends in this town, it is a path that starts from the Winter Park and has 7.8 kilometers of route. Thanks to it is paved, it is ideal to walk through it on foot, by bike or even with the baby cart.\n\nThe path runs along the old narrow railroad track and running through it is the old La Manjoya station, which is currently occupied by a nature classroom. In the last section, you can see old mills, as well as the riparian forest.\n\nThis route ends at the old train station of Fuso de la Reina. If you want to return to Oviedo, you will have to do the same route but in reverse, because it is a journey. However, you can also return by train, taking it in the current station of this town, which is a few meters ahead.</string>
    <string name="sendaverde_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Naranco Mountain -->
    <string name="montenaranco_title">Naranco Mountain</string>
    <string name="montenaranco_info">It is a 5-kilometer-long mountain range that surrounds the city of Oviedo. El Pico Paisano is its highest peak, with 632 meters of height. In this peak is the large sculpture of the Sacred Heart of Jesus, visible from virtually any point of the capital and attraction of tourists visiting Oviedo. From there you get a unique view of the capital, besides being an ideal place to relax and connect with nature.\n\nBut in addition to this, in this mountain are the main jewels of Asturian pre-Romanesque, Santa María del Naranco and San Miguel de Lillo, as well as other attractions such as the Finnish track or other paths designed for hiking. Thanks to these routes, it is possible to arrive from the capital to Pico Paisano in about an hour and a quarter.</string>
    <string name="montenaranco_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Guanga Waterfall Route -->
    <string name="rutacascadasguanga_title">Guanga Waterfall Route</string>
    <string name="rutacascadasguanga_info">The Cascadas del Guanga are in the council of Oviedo, just over 20 minutes from Las Caldas Villa Termal by car.\n\nThe show is guaranteed on this route through forests of oak, beech and chestnut trees. Short route that begins next to a laundry on the road that connects San Andrés, with Castañeo del Monte.\n\nIn the route classified as easy or intermediate difficulty, we will find the odd slope, which we will raffle without problems and that will make us reach the waterfalls. The walk of about 3.5 km round trip and about two hours will allow to see two important waterfalls as well as 5 minor waterfalls</string>
    <string name="rutacascadasguanga_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Priorio -->
    <string name="priorio_title">Priorio</string>
    <string name="priorio_info">It is a parish belonging to the municipality of Oviedo located 10 kilometers from the capital. It is made up of the towns of Las Caldas, Casielles, Cuesta Ayones, La Piñera, La Premaña and Priorio.\n\nThis town has several outstanding monuments. One of them is the Romanesque Church of San Juan de Priorio, which is located a few meters from the resort of Las Caldas. Another tourist attraction in the area are the Prehistoric Caves of the Lluera, which have been declared a Site of Cultural Interest because they contain a series of Paleolithic representations. And also it emphasizes the Castle of Priorio, that belongs to the Bishopric of Oviedo, old strength of century XIX built on the ruins of the original palace, constructed by Alfonso II the Chaste.\n\nIt is a good leisure option to visit this parish on a sunny day and take advantage not only to contemplate the different monuments and caves, but also to benefit from the medicinal waters of the Las Caldas spa.</string>
    <string name="priorio_timetable"></string>

    <!-- San Francisco Field -->
    <string name="camposanfrancisco_title">San Francisco Field</string>
    <string name="camposanfrancisco_info">The field of San Francisco, popularly known as El Campo by the ovetenses, is an urban park located in the very center of Oviedo. It is one of the most significant places of the capital of the Principality of Asturias and authentic lung of the city.\n\nLocated in the center of the city, delimited by a set of streets: the one of Uría, to the east; that of Count Toreno, to the north; that of the Marquis of Santa Cruz, to the south; and for that of Santa Susana, to the west, thus giving rise to a rhomboidal shape.\n\nInside you can distinguish several walks and avenues: Paseo de los Álamos, Paseo del Bombé, Paseo de José Cuesta, Avenida Italia or Avenida Alemania, among others.\n\nLos Álamos walk is parallel to Uría street, while Bombé forms a subtle acute angle with Santa Susana street. The avenues of Italy and Germany connect the walks of the Alamos and Bombé.\n\nCurrently, the City Council uses the facilities of the park to hold music events and concerts within the cultural program of the city of Oviedo.</string>
    <string name="camposanfrancisco_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Las Caldas Golf Course -->
    <string name="campogolflascaldas_title">Las Caldas Golf Course</string>
    <string name="campogolflascaldas_info">It is a municipal golf course located 5 kilometers from Oviedo, in the town of Las Caldas. It was inaugurated in the year 2000 and has 18 holes, par 71. It is a real challenge for lovers of this sport, due to its high degree of difficulty.\n\nThe field is located in the middle of a natural place in the center of the Asturian province. While practicing this sport, players can enjoy beautiful views of the surroundings, plagued by trees such as oaks, chestnut trees and cherry trees.\n\nIn order to enjoy a fantastic day of golf, it is possible to rent the necessary equipment in its facilities. In addition, it has the necessary facilities so that players can spend the entire day in the field, as is the case of a restaurant or a clubhouse.</string>
    <string name="campogolflascaldas_timetable">Monday 08:30 – 21:30\nTuesday 08:30 – 21:30\nWednesday 08:30 – 21:30\nThursday 08:30 – 21:30\nFriday 08:30 – 21:30\nSaturday 08:30 – 21:30\nSunday 08:30 – 21:30</string>

    <!-- Route of wines -->
    <string name="rutavinos_title">Route of wines</string>
    <string name="rutavinos_info">One of the favorite places of leisure of the ovetenses is the route of the wines, that has been gaining popularity in the last years. It is a succession of bars located in Manuel Pedregal and Campoamor streets, near the train station and a few meters from Uría street. The Wine Route consists of almost twenty establishments with small terraces, which makes it a valid option for the whole year.\n\nThe undisputed protagonist is wine, however, it is also possible to enjoy a beer or a drink. Enjoy a good atmosphere any day of the week, especially in the late afternoon and on Sunday mornings. Undoubtedly, its fame is due to the wide gastronomic offer, where tapas and various tostas stand out, although it is also possible to taste traditional Asturian dishes.</string>
    <string name="rutavinos_timetable"></string>

    <!-- Gascona - The Cider Boulevard -->
    <string name="gascona_title">Gascona - The Cider Boulevard</string>
    <string name="gascona_info">Everyone knows that Asturias is the capital of cider par excellence. Due to the success that this drink has among the tourists and the Asturians themselves, one of the busiest streets of the capital of the Principality is the Gascona street, also known as The Cider Boulevard, and located in the heart of Oviedo.\n\nThe place name \'Gascona\' is related to the French province of Gascony, due to the important free population that settled near the current Oviedo street, attracted by the Jacobean Route.\n\nIt gathers around thirteen cider houses, where you can enjoy not only the Asturian drink par excellence, but also its gastronomy, valued positively internationally with dishes as recognizable as the Asturian fabada, the cachopo, the buns preñaos or the frixuelos, from a very wide variety. All this can be enjoyed under a relaxed and festive atmosphere typical of the Asturian culture.</string>
    <string name="gascona_timetable"></string>

    <!-- El Fontán Market -->
    <string name="mercadofontan_title">El Fontán Market</string>
    <string name="mercadofontan_info">In the historic center of Oviedo, and just a few meters from the Plaza del Ayuntamiento, is the ideal place to go if you want to take a walk in which the scents, flavors and sensations that come from the best more typical Asturian products.\n\nThis market located in the center of the capital dates back to the sixteenth century, when the Emperor Charles V gives the Asturian capital a free market to overcome the local economy, but it is not until 1885 when the building we know today is built, It is characterized by its warm natural lighting provided by its large windows and its open space that causes a sense of order.\n\nIn addition to the best ingredients necessary for the realization of the typical dishes of the region's gastronomy, in this market you can also buy other typical handicrafts, such as madreñas, typical footwear in rural areas of Asturias.</string>
    <string name="mercadofontan_timetable">Monday 08:00 – 15:30\nTuesday 08:00 – 15:30\nWednesday 08:00 – 15:30\nThursday 08:00 – 15:30\nFriday 08:00 – 15:30\nSaturday 08:00 – 15:30\nSunday closed</string>
</resources>